readyflowers.com.au 2006-06-23

# Ready Flowers Australia - Fresh flowers delivered Australia wide same day.

Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information

Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists does not read any of your private online communications.

Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists and Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists family of Web sites.

Use of your Personal Information

Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists collects and uses your personal information to operate the Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists and its affiliates. Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists, in order to determine what Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists, or the public.

Use of Cookies

The Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists pages, or register with Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists site or services, a cookie helps Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists services or Web sites you visit.

Security of your Personal Information

Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Changes to this Statement

Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists is protecting your information.

Contact Information

Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Ready Flowers - Send Flowers Australia wide with real Australian Florists at [admin@readyflowers.com.au](mailto:admin@readyflowers.com.au). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
